import { Question } from "../App";

export const crashLandingData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is the profession of Yoon Se-ri, the main female character?",
            "options": ["CEO", "Doctor", "Teacher", "Journalist"],
            "answer": "CEO"
        },
        {
            "question": "How does Yoon Se-ri end up in North Korea?",
            "options": ["Paragliding accident", "Plane crash", "Car accident", "Boat accident"],
            "answer": "Paragliding accident"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the main male character who helps Yoon Se-ri in North Korea?",
            "options": ["Ri Jeong-hyeok", "Kim Joo-mok", "Lee Jung-hyeok", "Park Jung-woo"],
            "answer": "Ri Jeong-hyeok"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Ri Jeong-hyeok's profession?",
            "options": ["Soldier", "Doctor", "Police officer", "Businessman"],
            "answer": "Soldier"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Yoon Se-ri's family company?",
            "options": ["Seri's Group", "Hae-woo Corporation", "Seryeong Group", "Hae-myeong Inc."],
            "answer": "Seri's Group"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Ri Jeong-hyeok’s brother and what is his profession?",
            "options": ["Ri Jeong-hyeok", "Ri Jeong-woo, a high-ranking official", "Ri Jeong-sik, a businessman", "Ri Jeong-jo, a soldier"],
            "answer": "Ri Jeong-woo, a high-ranking official"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the restaurant owned by Yoon Se-ri's friend in North Korea?",
            "options": ["The Greenhouse", "The Red Lantern", "The Pine Tree", "The Maple Leaf"],
            "answer": "The Greenhouse"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does Yoon Se-ri give to Ri Jeong-hyeok as a gift?",
            "options": ["A brooch", "A watch", "A scarf", "A ring"],
            "answer": "A brooch"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the North Korean soldier who becomes Yoon Se-ri’s bodyguard?",
            "options": ["Gu Seung-joon", "Kim Jong-gil", "Choi Ji-hoon", "Park Kwang-beom"],
            "answer": "Gu Seung-joon"
        },
        {
            "question": "What song does Yoon Se-ri perform at the end of the series?",
            "options": ["The Greatest Love of All", "Here Comes the Sun", "I Will Always Love You", "The Way We Were"],
            "answer": "The Greatest Love of All"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the group of North Korean soldiers who assist Ri Jeong-hyeok and Yoon Se-ri?",
            "options": ["The Brave Soldiers", "The Loyal Squad", "The Gentlemen", "The Black Hawks"],
            "answer": "The Gentlemen"
        }
    ]
